我叫巴里·艾伦
My name is Barry Allen,
是现今世上速度最快的人
and I am the fastest man alive.
在外人看来
To the outside world,
我只是个普通的鉴证专员
I'm an ordinary forensic scientist,
但在尖端科研实验室的朋友们的帮助下
but secretly, with the help of my friends at S.T.A.R. Labs,
我秘密地打击犯罪  寻找跟我一样的超能力者
I fight crime and find other meta-humans like me.
但当我女儿从未来时空前来帮忙
But when my daughter came back from the future to help,
她改变了现在
she changed the present,
现在我们的世界比以往更加危险
and now our world is more dangerous than ever,
我是唯一一个来得及拯救世界的人
and I'm the only one fast enough to save it.
我是闪电侠
I am the Flash.
《闪电侠》前情回顾  我还是自己来发吧
Previously on "The Flash"...I'll deliver it myself.
那是艾尔伯德·斯旺  逆闪
That is Eobard Thawne, the Reverse Flash.
-他杀死了我母亲  -我不知道这些
- He killed my mother. - I didn't know that.
我的生活比过去好了很多
My life is a million times better
这都是因为你  格蕾西
and it's all because of you, Gracie.
她可能醒不过来了
She may never wake.
每个超能力者都得死
Every meta will die.
这是一份蝉的DNA样本
This is a DNA sample from Cicada.
我们能做治愈超能力者的解药
We can make a meta-human cure.
如果打败他的关键是打动他的心
What if the key to defeating him is appealing to his heart?
-我们要怎么做  -拯救他的孩子
- How do we do that? - By saving his child.
我们要让格雷丝苏醒
We need to wake up Grace.
请你想一想
I want you to think about
你生命中最大的秘密
the biggest secret in your life.
你瞒着你爱的人甚至你自己的
The one you keep from the people that you love
那个秘密
or even from yourself.
请你想象一下  如果那个秘密被揭穿
I want you to imagine what would happen
会怎么样
if that secret got out.
还记得你问我的这个问题吗
Remember when you asked me that?
我一直在遵循你的训练
I've been using all of your training.
研究我的脉搏  管理微表情
Studying my pulse, managing micro-expressions,
控制不协调的手势
limiting non-congruent gestures,
销毁一切证据
destroying any piece of evidence.
我不知道还能坚持多久
I don't know how much longer I can keep this up.
不仅仅因为这样做的风险
And not just because of the risks.
[填词游戏]
而是因为我越是接触我爸妈
But because the closer I get to my parents,
我就越觉得我在伤害他们
the more I feel like I'm hurting them.
数据输入完毕  吉迪恩
Data entry complete, Gideon.
谢谢  诺拉·韦斯特艾伦
Thank you, Nora West-Allen.
要把它发给同一个接受者吗
Shall I send this to the usual recipient?
是的
Yes.
发给艾尔伯德·斯旺
Send it to Eobard Thawne,
优先级别急件
priority level urgent.
闪 电 侠
第五季
第十二集
你准备好了吗
You ready for this?
爸爸  我还... 我还不够快
Dad, I'm just--I'm not fast enough yet.
现在不许退出了  这是你这辈子最重要的赛跑
No backing out now, this is the biggest race of your life.
-准备好  预备  走  -还没  爸爸  爸爸...
- Get ready, set, go! - Not really. Dad, Dad--
等等  天哪
Wait, wait! Oh, God.
扶住了
Gotcha.
太丢人了
This is so embarrassing.
我在口袋伙伴上玩溜冰游戏可厉害了
I'm really good at the ice skating game on my Pocket Pal!
好了  你弯一下膝盖
Okay, you're just gonna bend your knees...
-好  -然后往前倾一点
- Kay. - And lead forward a little.
就这样  对了
Just, yeah.
对了
Yeah.
-我会了  -你会了
- I'm doing it. - You're doing it.
我会滑冰了  这城市真是酷炫  妈妈
I'm skating. This is like schway city, Mom.
谢了
Thanks.
瞧你们
Look at you guys.
-真会当妈  -怎么  那你呢
- Such a mom. - What? What about you?
滑冰和游戏之夜可是你的点子啊
You're the one who sprang for ice skating and game night.
我知道  自从诺拉受伤了
Yeah, well, I know when Nora got hurt,
我就有点沮丧
I got a little frustrated.
而现在我们有阻止蝉的切实计划了
And now, I mean, we have an actual plan to stop Cicada.
唤醒他侄女来打动他的心
Waking up his niece to appeal to his heart.
我知道德怀尔是个杀手  但他毕竟是个人
I know Dwyer's a killer, but he's still a person,
就像我们爱诺拉一样  他也爱格蕾丝
and he loves Grace just like we love Nora.
我也不知道  我只是觉得
So I don't know. I just feel like
一切都在往好的方向发展
everything's heading in the right direction.
我来了  来了  上吧
Here I come. Coming in. Here we go.
不好意思  你为什么带个头盔
I'm sorry, why are you wearing a helmet?
你不是橡胶做的吗
I thought you were made of rubber.
总有人得给孩子们做个榜样
Somebody's gotta set a good example for these kids.
我以为你在冰上长大的呢
Well--I thought you grew up on the ice.
算是吧
Well, I did, basically,
我妈跟磨冰机驾驶员约过会  所以...
my mom dated a zamboni operator, so...
在我来的地方可没人跟磨冰机司机约会
And I tell you where I'm from we don't date zamboni drivers.
为什么呢  因为那里没有磨冰机
Why is that? Because there are no zambonis.
那我们怎么清理冰  我们整个冬天
How do we clear the ice? All winter long,
手里拿个刮刀  趴在地上
we are on our hands and knees with a squeegee in hand.
我告诉你
Let me tell you.
那是他一年里最爽的八个月
Best eight months of the year for this guy.
故事真动听  夏洛克
It's a really great story, Sherlock.
歇洛克
Sherloque.
说到刮冰
You know, speaking of squeegeeing,
有个人确实需要刮一刮冰了
you know who could use a good squeegeeing
拉里·布卢门撒尔  他死了
is Larry Blumenthal. He's dead.
-拉里·布卢门撒尔死了  -对
- Larry Blumenthal is dead? - Yeah.
住你家过道对面那个专利登记员
The patent registrar across the hall from you
建筑面积400平那个...
with the 400 square footage--
-还有庭院的那个  -对  死翘翘了
- And the courtyard views? - Yeah, dead as a doornail.
如果那块地方你想要  就给你租吧
You can have that place if you want it. Yours to rent.
什么  天哪  太棒了
What? Oh, my God. This is perfect.
我的广告收益这季度涨了  那...
I mean, my ad revenue has been up this quarter, so...
对  有了多余的地方
Yeah, with the extra space you'd be able to hire
你可以雇编辑和摄影师了
editors, photographers.
我可以把我的博客变成真正的报纸了
I could turn my blog into a real newspaper.
我的包裹到了
Oh, my package has arrived.
什么包裹
What package?
里面是我们所有问题的解决办法
This is the solution to all our problems.
朋友们  我们得走了
Allez, les amis. We must go.
女士们  先生们
Madames et monsieurs,
我向各位介绍这台记忆机
may I present to you la Machine à Mémoire,
或者在美国  人们把这叫做
or as they say in Amérique, you know...
记忆机器
The Memory Machine.
没错  爱瑞丝  记忆机器  很多次
Oui, Iris. Memory Machine. Many times...
我进入过人们的大脑
I have entered into people's minds
用的正是这台机器
using this very technology.
从夏日林研究所里
From the unfortunate comatose victims
不幸昏迷的伤者乃至...  没错
of the Summerholt Institute to, yes,
杰维斯·泰奇本人
Jervis Tetch himself,
蝙蝠侠主要反派之一
地球221的恐怖杀人狂魔疯帽子
the Terrible Mad Hatter Killer from Earth-221.
我才刚从唐豪瑟站点回来
I come back from Tannhauser for one second,
想借个连接器来研制超能力者解药
just borrowing a splicer for the meta cure
看我发现了什么
and what do I find?
-这个...  -记忆机
- This, this-- - Machine à Mémoire.
管它呢  你怎么把它从地球221弄过来的
Whatever. How did you even get this here from Earth-221?
我用的是"先驱者多元宇宙快递服务"
Well, I used the Forerunner Multiversal Delivery Service.
你们不用吗  你们没办金卡吗
You don't use it? You don't have a gold card like me?
也许我可以给你拿个折扣
Maybe I'll get you a discount.
我们不需要折扣
We don't need a discount.
我们只要唤醒格蕾丝
All right, we just need to wake up Grace.
这台机器会唤醒她吧
This'll wake her up, right?
大多数昏迷的病人
So in most coma patients,
大脑活动频繁的区域进入休眠状态时
high traffic areas of brain activity go dormant
低频活动区域就会活跃起来
and the low traffic areas spring to life,
但很可惜  格蕾丝和一般人不同
but unfortunately, Grace isn't normal.
她昏迷的时间不仅比一般人长
Not only has her coma lasted longer than the average,
而且她的意识已经自行隔离在一个
but her consciousness has isolated itself
特定的区域了
into one specific region,
也就是她的长期记忆
her long-term memories.
对你来说肯定是小菜一碟
It will be so facile, easy peasy for you.
只要把你们的脑电波
All you do is you transmit your brainwaves
传输至格蕾丝的记忆里对吧
into Grace's memories, right?
然后你们就能把她的意识
And then you'll lead her consciousness
带出神经联结传送门
out of a neural nexus portal.
格蕾丝就能醒过来了
And Grace awakens.
有点像思考者困住我的时候
It's sort of like when Barry woke me up
巴里唤醒我那样
when the Thinker trapped me.
出奇的是  听起来是很简单
Surprisingly, that sounds kind of easy peasy.
只要格蕾丝异常的脑损伤
As long as Grace's unusual brain damage
不会引发任何意外的风险就行
doesn't cause any unforeseen risks.
所以我才建议你们
This is why I suggest you travel in pairs
两人一组来使用这台机器
when you're using this technology.
每次我用这台机器进入某个人的记忆时
Every time I enter into someone's memories
我肯定是和我搭档一起
when I use this I went with my partner for sure.
你搭档不会碰巧是华生吧
Your partner's name didn't happen to be Watson, did it?
不是  他不叫"华生"
No, his name was not Watson.
他叫华苏
His name was Watsune.
没错  我们一起看过十几个人的大脑
Yes, together we went through dozens of minds, together--
直到有一次  我发现自己
until one time I found myself
在蒙特利尔酒店房间的一段记忆里
in a memory of a motel room in Montreal
而在那段记忆里  我当场发现
where what do I find but Watsune in flagrante deli
华苏和我妻子有染
in interpersonal relationship with my wife,
虽然是第四任
fourth wife, but still.
你是说可以看到搭档的记忆吗
You're saying you could see your partner's memories?
有可能是两人一组的副作用
It's a possible side effect of traveling in pairs.
说到这个
And speaking of which,
哪两个人自愿参加这项任务
which pairs would like to volunteer for this mission?
我建议两位极速者  这样任务就能极速完成
I suggest the speedsters for this to be accomplished so quick.
-好  -就你们俩了
- Yeah. - Elected.
如果你看到我偷拼字游戏空白方块的记忆
Hey, if you see a memory of me stealing blank Scrabble tile
事情不是那样的好吗
it's not what it looks like, all right?
这个不错  老爸
That's a good one, Dad.
剩下的就是把这个收发器磁盘
All that is left is to connect this transceiver disc
连接到格蕾丝的电图仪上  就能传输了
to Grace's EEG and we can transmit.
-好  -好
- Great. - Right.
明天第一件事
All right, first thing tomorrow,
拯救格蕾丝
we save Grace.
今晚有什么大计划吗
Any big plans for the night off?
我要睡觉
I'm gonna crash.
冰霜杀手看了一整晚的电影
Killer Frost was up all night watching movies
她最爱的吴宇森和约翰·休斯
from her two favorite Johns, Woo and Hughes.
我本人更喜欢福特和沃特斯
Huh, I'm more of a Ford and Waters man myself,
但我今晚要继续通宵熬夜
but I will be up all night yet again
研究你们带给我的辐射超能力者血样
working with the radiated meta-human sample you guys got me.
这个解药还缺少些成分
There's something missing with this cure.
好的  晚点见
All right, I'll see you guys later.
-好  -晚安
- All right. - Night.
我也忽略了一点
You know, there's something that I'm missing too.
-你刚刚愈合的双手  -奇怪的用词
- Your freshly healed hands. - Odd choice of words.
今晚我要去见一个线人
Well, I'm meeting with an informant tonight
他也许知道德怀尔的下落
and he might have a lead on Dwyer's location,
但我不确定我是否应该相信他
but I'm not sure if I should trust him.
所以你要我对他使用震波
So you need me to vibe him. Look, man.
我真的应该好好研制这个解药
I should really be working on this cure.
但是我的连接器计算要
But my splicer algorithm won't technically be done
凌晨三点才完成
until 3:00 A.M.
谢谢你  这个线索非常重要
Thanks, man, this is, this is really important work.
好
Okay.
吉迪恩  我要怎么入侵这台机器
Okay, Gideon, how do I hack this thing
才能不让老爸看到我的记忆
so that Dad won't see my memories?
无论任何配置
In any configuration,
如果你和巴里·艾伦一起进入
if you and Barry Allen go in together,
你仍然有暴露自己记忆的风险
you still risk exposing your memories.
所以我什么也做不了
So I can't do anything.
吉迪恩  那是...
Gideon, is that...
格蕾丝·吉本斯的脑电波
Grace Gibbons' brain waves.
看来歇洛克·威尔斯已经放入接收器磁盘了
It would appear Sherloque Wells has planted the transceiver disc.
所以我可以一个人进去
So I can go in alone.
我会在大家发现之前回来
And I'll be back before anyone notices,
但是那时  格蕾丝早就醒了
but by that time Grace'll be awake anyway.
启动激动脑电波传输
Activating brain wave transmission.
三  二  一
In three, two, one.
中城警局
CCPD?
乔西  这就是那孩子
Okay, Jones, here's the kid.
我们发现她躲在车座下边
We found her in the car hiding under the seat.
超能力者袭击时她父母在取款机旁
Her parents were at the ATM when the meta attacked.
真惨  我们找到她其他亲属了吗
Damn. We located her next of kin?
可能有个叔叔  还在追查
Maybe an uncle. Still tracking down
他最后的所在地
his last known address.
她不能睡在这长凳上
Well, she can't sleep on this bench.
我们得把她送走
We've gotta get her out of here.
天啊  可怜的孩子
God, poor kid.
你是谁  你能看到吗
Who are you? You can see me?
对了  你是格蕾丝旧记忆里的
Oh, right, you're Grace's consciousness
潜意识
in her old memory.
我是诺拉
I'm Nora.
你能带我去找我家人吗
Can you take me to my parents?
不行  我做不到
No, um, I can't,
但你跟我来  我可以让你感觉更好些
but if you come with me, I can help you feel better.
你知道吗
You know,
我在你这个年龄时也有个这样的朋友
when I was your age, I had a friend just like this.
我想他也想感觉更好些
I bet he'd like to feel better too.
好吧
Okay.
好了  格蕾丝  我来带你走进
All right, Gracie, let's get you through
这个传送门  从昏迷中醒来
this portal and out of your coma
赶在有人发现我溜进这里这之前
before anyone notices I snuck in here.
不好
Oh, no.
不要  不要  不要
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
糟了
Oh, no.
我被困住了
I'm trapped.
我们会找到出路的  我保证
We're gonna find a way out of here, I promise.
我感觉在这警局里呆了好久
I feel like I've been in this police station for a long time,
现在要永远在这里了吗
and now I'm gonna be here forever, aren't I?
让我一人待会
Just leave me alone.
你知道吗  我在你这个年龄的时候
You know, when I was your age,
我要自己独自一人来到
I had to come to this very same police station
这个警局
all by myself too.
-这里挺可怕的  -我没有在害怕
- It's kind of scary in here. - I'm not scared.
我曾是  我总是很害怕
Well, I was. I'm scared all the time.
实际上  有一回有一个很坏的家伙
In fact, once, there was this really bad guy
他想要伤害飞机上的很多人
and he wanted to hurt a whole lot of people on a plane.
超能力者吗
A meta?
但我阻止了他
But I helped stop him.
-真的吗  -我可是怕极了
- Whoa, really? - I was terrified, though.
但你知道我的秘密是什么吗
But you know what my secret is?
我就是去幻想成功之后会怎样
I just imagine what will happen after I do the thing.
你想试试吗
Do you want to try it?
好的  闭上你的眼睛
Okay, close your eyes,
想想你出去之后要干什么
and think about what will happen once you're out of here.
我要去见奥林叔叔
I'll see Uncle Orlin.
咱们找办法出去吧  如何
Let's find our way out of here, okay?
所以我不能用"公报"  "记录"
So I can't use "Gazette"? "Chronicle"?
所以唯一能用的名字是"中城市民"
So the only name that's cleared is "Central City Citizen."
好好  谢谢
Uh, yeah, yeah, thanks.
电话里的是谁
Hey, who was that on the phone?
一个律师  她在帮我解答一些
Um, a lawyer, she was helping answer some questions
开报社的问题
about me starting a newspaper.
真不错  她怎么说
That's cool. What'd she say?
无所谓了
You know, it doesn't matter.
我觉得现在时机不好
I-I'm actually not sure that the timing is right,
我只想要集中精力在闪电小队上
and I really just want to focus on team Flash
一起阻止蝉
and stopping Cicada.
是  但是...
Yeah, but--
等下
Oh, hold on.
慢点  慢点
Slow down, slow down.
是歇洛克
It's Sherloque.
诺拉做了什么
Nora did what?
为什么诺拉一个人进去了
Why would Nora go in alone?
为什么她还没出来
And why isn't she out yet?
我目前的理论是  格蕾丝受损的大脑
My working theory is that Grace's unique brain damage
让她表现得非常有防御倾向
has caused her brain to act defensively,
所以当它察觉到外界存在
so when it sensed an outside presence,
它移动了所有神经线路
it moved all of its neural nexus pathways
封锁了出口  像是一种隔离封锁
to seal the exits like a-a quarantine procedure.
格蕾丝的大脑认为诺拉是病毒
Grace's brain thinks Nora's a pathogen.
是的  我们可能会看到突触防御系统
Yes, we can expect its synaptic defense mechanisms
试图消灭她
to try and eliminate her.
记得我跟你说过关于疯帽人的故事吗
Remember I told you about the Mad Hatter?
他同样是脑部受伤  所以在我与
He was also brain damaged, so after my dispute with
华苏和第四任妻子争执后  华苏独自去
Watsune and my fourth wife, Watsune pursued the case
追查案件  直到有一天我发现他
on his own until the day I found him
被连在一台记忆机器上  脑死亡了
hooked up to the Machine à Mémoire brain-dead.
你知道有这个可能性
You knew this was a possibility?
你说过的小事一碟呢
What happened to easy peasy?
这就是为什么我说两人一起进
That's why I say go in in pairs.
巴里  我们要进去找她
Barry, we have to go in after her.
我找遍了中城警局
I looked all over CCPD.
没有看到传送门的迹象
There's no sign of the portal.
你怎么能看到所有地方
How could you have looked everywhere?
你才走开两秒多钟
You were gone for about two seconds.
我速度很快
Well, I'm really fast.
我在高中时候练过长跑
I-I used to run track in high school.
中城松鼠队加油
Go CC Squirrels.
格蕾丝  你能带我去其他地方吗
Look, Grace, is there anywhere else you can take me?
其他的记忆
Another memory?
我们在哪里
Where are we?
我的家
My house.
奥林叔叔
Uncle Orlin!
你好啊  孩子
Hey, kiddo.
你怎么样  今天过得如何
How you doing? How was your day?
让我再捋一遍
Let me run through this again.
所以特鲁克先生  你说在这里看到了蝉
So Mr. Truck, you said. You've seen Cicada here?
那家伙像个讨厌的真菌一样赖在这里
Dude's been up in here like a mean fungus.
我知道了  白俄罗斯黑客什么样的
I see, and how is the White Russian Hacker?
你能集中下注意力吗
You wanna focus up here?
你能告诉我他暴力吗
So can you tell me was he violent?
很对  每周四
Hell yeah, every Thursday,
他都过来袭击这里的人
comes in and assaults anyone in here
没必要这样
Unnecessary.
但也行吧
But okay.
[萨卡达]
你说的是一个叫"萨卡达"的乐队吗
You're talking about a band named "Sickada"?
是啊  哥们
Yeah, bro.
你说"那个家伙"袭击了人们
You said "That dude" assaulted people.
他用烂透了的音乐袭击这里的每个人
He assaults everyone in here with that terrible music.
德比
Dibs.
没有像我希望的那样取得进展
Well, that didn't pan out the way that I hoped.
我们要有两个岳母了  拜托
We will have two Mother-In-Laws, please.
不不不不  特鲁克  谢谢你抽出空
No, no, no, no. Truck, thank you for your time.
-我觉得可以收工了  -来一杯吧
- I think we're done here. - One drink.
我付钱
I'm paying.
来一杯  但仅仅是因为
One drink, but only because
你从来没为任何东西付过钱  我很好奇
you never pay for anything ever and I'm really curious
太阳从西边出来什么样
to see what hell looks like frozen over.
不能提醒她我们来了吗
We can't warn her we're coming?
我们想安装一个紧急信标
We wanted to install an emergency beacon,
但是不起作用
but it didn't work.
你们进入以后  它就会创造一个新传送门
So once you enter, it'll create a new portal.
在格蕾丝的大脑封闭之前
You'll only have a few moments to find Grace and Nora
你们只有很短的时间去找格蕾丝和诺拉
before Grace's brain tries to seal it off.
记住  如果你们在里面死了...
Remember, if you die in there...
我们在外面也死了  我记得迪沃的事
We die out here. I remember from DeVoe.
我们会救她的  我保证
We're gonna save her, I promise.
开始脑波传输
Commencing brainwave transmission.
祝你们好运
Good luck.
中城警局
CCPD.
好了  来吧
All right, come on.
我们发现她藏在最后一辆车的座位下面
We found her hiding in the last car under the seat.
-她的父母呢  -不知道
- And her parents? - No idea.
她在去市区的红色专线上
She was on the Red Line headed downtown.
肯定是在第四街和韦德交汇处跳车了
Must've jumped the turnstile at Fourth and Waid.
我们不能就让她睡在长椅上
We can't just let her sleep on this bench.
天哪  巴里
Oh, my God. Barry.
等等  那是乔·韦斯特的孙女吗
Wait, is that Joe West's granddaughter?
诺拉  诺拉
Nora? Hey, Nora.
来人抓住她
Someone get her.
我觉得我们不在格蕾丝的记忆里
I don't think we're in Grace's memories.
是诺拉的记忆
We're in Nora's.
格蕾丝的大脑活动没有变化
There's been no changes in Grace's brain activity.
但你看
But look.
诺拉的大脑活动增加了三倍
Nora's brain activity has tripled.
这意味着...
That means...
巴里和爱瑞丝在诺拉的记忆里
Barry and Iris are in Nora's memories.
我们怎么会到了诺拉的童年记忆里
How did we end up in Nora's childhood memories?
我不知道  我也不清楚
I have no idea. I also have no clue
我们要怎么从这里救出诺拉
how we're gonna rescue Nora from here.
好吧  我们在一段记忆的记忆里  对吗
Okay. Okay, we're in a memory within a memory, right?
是的
Yeah.
所以如果我们通过一个传送门  那么...
So if we went through a portal, then...
就能带我们通向格蕾丝
It should take us into Grace.
是的  我们需要在诺拉的记忆里搜寻
Okay, yeah, we just have to wander through Nora's memories
直到发现传送门在哪
until we find where the portal went.
好的
Okay.
或许她会带我们去那里
Maybe she'll lead us right there.
这里怎么回事
What happened here?
我猜在诺拉的未来里  尖端科研实验室就是
I guess in Nora's future, S.T.A.R. Labs is--
-闪电侠博物馆  -闪电侠博物馆
- The Flash Museum. - The Flash Museum.
不会吧
No way.
看看这个
Look at this.
闪电侠玩具和闪电侠电话
Flash toys and Flash phones.
闪电侠戒指  开玩笑吗
Flash rings. Are you kidding? Wow.
这一切都会印到你的脑子里  对吗
This is all gonna go to your head, isn't it?
你知道吗  看来有可能哦
Oh, you know what? It looks like it might.
这个太可爱了
Oh, that is very cute.
我找到她了
Hey, I found her.
你觉得我们能和他说话吗
You think we can talk to her?
不  我倒是希望
No. I wish.
这可能是我唯一见到这个年纪的她的机会
This might be the only time I get to see her at this age.
但诺拉的意识不在这里
Nora's consciousness isn't here, though.
是在格蕾丝那里  这是个固定的记忆
It's in Grace. This is a fixed memory.
我们不能干扰
We can't interfere.
我十岁的时候  从来没有离家出走过
When I was ten, I wasn't running away from home.
那是因为你是个好孩子
That's 'cause you were a good kid.
我总是离家出走
I ran away all the time.
是啊  只是因为你想要见你爸爸
Yeah, only 'cause you were trying to see your dad.
而不是你想逃离某个人
Not 'cause you were running from someone.
我们应该继续去找传送门
Oh, hey, we should keep trying to find the portal.
闪电侠
拜托  格蕾丝  不要抱怨
Come on, Gracie, no cussing.
拜托  我们来吧  好吗
Please, can we, please?
好吧  可以
Okay, fine.
一只稀有的老鸟是鹈鹕  嘴能装的东西
A rare, old bird is a pelican whose beak can hold more
比肚子还多
than his belly can.
他的嘴可以装下一个星期的食物
He can hold in his beak enough food for a week.
但如果我知道他怎么做到的话就怪了
But I'm darned if I know how the hell he can.
格蕾丝  或许我们现在可以走了
Grace, I was thinking maybe we could go now
然后去找传送门
and look for the portal?
什么东西烧着了吗
Is something burning?
糟了
Oh, crap.
我是说  脏东西
I mean, crud.
他觉得现在是他在照顾我
He thinks he takes care of me now,
但其实是我在照顾他
but I really take care of him.
好了  孩子  你最好都吃了
Okay, kiddo, you better eat up.
今天是个大日子
We've got a big day.
这是...
This is...
首先我们去动物园...
First we're going to the zoo...
这是一个有趣的玩偶之家
This is an interesting doll house.
我们要去买冰淇淋  然后...
We're gonna get ice cream, and then...
别忘了游乐场
Can't forget the fair.
游乐场
Fair?
你受伤的地方
Where you got hurt.
格蕾丝  我认为传送门就在那里
Grace, I-I think that's where the portal is.
你可以带我去那里吗
Can you take me there?
去你能记得的最后一个地方
To the last place that you remember?
好
Okay.
看看她
Hey, check her out.
她正是你喜欢的类型  你应该请她喝一杯
She's right up your alley. You should buy her a drink.
真的  看她衣服上的手工缝线
Damn. Look at that hand stitching.
不行  我不是来这里欣赏外套的
No, no, I did not come here to admire jackets.
我是来用震波获取消息的
I came here to vibe and inform.
是只有我这样觉得  还是
Is it just me or are there a lot
这里真的有很多穿皮衣的女士
of ladies in leather in here?
今天是单身之夜
Yep, singles night.
-真是巧了  -是吗
- It's quite a coincidence. - Is it?
你经常说什么来着
What is it you're always saying?
-我察觉到了秘密  -这句话是我的专利
- "I smell a mystery"? - That is trademarked.
我能用震波感应到你现在散发着焦虑
I can vibe the anxiety coming off of you right now.
整件事就是个圈套
This whole thing was a setup.
你的线人当然不认识蝉
Of course your informant didn't know Cicada.
我的意思是他听说过蝉
I mean, he knew of Cicada.
你骗了我  你浪费我的时间
You lied to me, you wasted my time
让我今晚来做你的搭讪帮手
so I could be your wingman tonight?
不  不是  兄弟  不是这样的
No, no, no, dude, it's not like that.
每次我觉得你变成熟的时候
You know, just when I think you're growing up,
你就会做出一些事  让我发现
you go ahead and do something that shows me
你还是像我们第一次见面时那样自私
you're just as selfish as the day we met.
这是酒钱
That's for the drinks.
失陪了
Excuse me.
反派
大厅
等等
Wait.
这些人还有专门的展厅吗
These guys get their own wing?
谁是蝉  官方认为...
Who is Cicada? Officials believe...
巴里  也许我们应该继续寻找传送门
Barry, maybe we should keep looking for the portal.
好的
Yeah.
但蝉在闪电侠消失后于2024年重现时
But when Cicada resurfaced in 2024 after the Flash vanished,
有人猜测蝉并不是人类
some were left to speculate that Cicada is not a man at all,
而是一个不死的怪物
but an immortal monster.
我们唯一能够确认的就是他杀了多少人
All we know for sure is his body count,
152名受害者  且数量正增加
152 victims and rising.
等等  什么
Wait, what?
我知道我们没有抓住蝉  但他一直在杀戮吗
I knew we never caught Cicada, but he never stops killing?
闪电侠做了他能做的一切
Flash did everything he could,
但是蝉杀死的人比极速
but Cicada killed more people than Zoom
甚至红色死神还多
or even the Red Death.
中城对闪电侠的看法  他未完成的事业
And the way the city saw the Flash, his legacy...
都变得不同了
it was never the same.
诺拉·韦斯特·艾伦  你有大麻烦了
Nora West-Allen, you are in serious trouble, young lady.
格蕾丝  我们来这里干什么
Grace, what are we doing here?
你想去我记忆里最后的地方
You wanted to go to my last memory.
是的  但我以为会是游乐场
Yeah, but I thought that was supposed to be at the fair.
格蕾丝
Grace?
有人吗
Hello?
这种毁灭性的现象来自一个
The destructive phenomenon emanated from a satellite
坠入衰退轨道的卫星
that had fallen into a decaying orbit.
幸运的是  在这个卫星撞击城市
Thankfully, before the satellite could strike the city...
她怎么会记得这个
How does she remember this?
灾难性事件
A catastrophic event...
一个新的超能力者被看到
A new meta was last seen jumping off a building
新超能力者相关
为了躲避追捕从楼上跳下
in order to evade capture after...
我得纠正这一切  格蕾西
I'm gonna make this right, Gracie.
每个超能力者都得死
Every meta will die.
格蕾丝  你那晚怎么会听到奥林的话
Grace, how did you hear Orlin that night?
-你陷入了昏迷  -我知道
- You were in a coma. - I know.
但是我一直在听着
But I've been listening.
-你必须得停下来  -等我完成之后再说
- You have to stop. - Not until I'm finished.
他们今晚去追你了吗
Did they come after you tonight?
我杀了他的搭档  震波
I killed his partner, Vibe,
但是还有一个女人
but there was a woman there too,
把我伤得很重
banged me up pretty bad.
她有神速力
She had speed.
我认为她是闪电侠的女儿
I think she's the Flash's daughter.
格蕾丝  我不知道你认为奥林说了什么
Grace, I don't know what you think Orlin said--
你说你每个地方都找过了
You said you looked everywhere.
我现在明白了  你有神速力
I get it now. You have speed.
你就是她  是吗
You're her, aren't you?
你是闪电侠的女儿
You're the Flash's daughter.
你就是伤害我舅舅的人
You're the one who hurt my uncle.
格蕾丝  我想帮你
Grace, I want to help you.
不  你不是  奥林舅舅对我说起过你
No, you don't. Uncle Orlin told me about you.
你和你爸爸想要伤害他
You and your dad are trying to hurt him.
那是因为他想伤害其他人
Only because he's trying to hurt other people,
无辜的人
innocent people!
不  他只伤害超能力者
No, he only hurts metas,
就像那个杀害我父母的人
like the one who killed my parents.
就像你  你是超能力者  还是个骗子
Like you! You're a meta and a liar!
不是所有超能力者都是坏人
All metas aren't bad.
我舅舅是英雄  他保护人们
My uncle is a hero. He protects people,
我要保护我舅舅
and I protect my uncle!
我的神速力消失了
My speed's gone.
你以为你能跑到
Did you think that you could run away
我找不到的地方吗
and I wouldn't figure out where you went?
我的工作就是找出真相  我是个记者
It's my job to find out the truth. I'm a reporter.
你总是说自己是记者
You're always a reporter.
为什么不能做一次妈妈
Why not be my mom for once?
是吗  我这样做你妈妈怎么样
Oh, yeah? How's this for being your mom?
你永远不许再来这里  快走
You are never coming back to this place again. Let's go.
等等  你口袋里是什么
Excuse me, what is in your pocket?
-马上把它给我  -这不是你的
- Hand that over right now. - It's not yours.
它现在是了  你要为自己的行为付出代价
Well, it is now. There are consequences to your actions.
给我
Hand it over.
我恨你
I hate you.
扔了吧  我们走
Leave it. Let's go.
爱瑞丝  那不是你
Iris, that wasn't you.
我知道  但将来是  巴里
Yeah, but it will be, Barry.
诺拉从小到大都会恨她的妈妈
Nora's gonna grow up hating her mother.
不  她不会的  你会做不同选择的
No, she won't. You're gonna make different choices.
如果你不想成为刚刚我们看到的那个人
If you don't wanna be that person that we just saw,
那就不要成为她
don't be that person.
我知道  你总是这么说  巴里
I know. I know you keep saying that, Barry,
那就是我正在努力做的事情
and that's what I'm trying to do.
我今天有那么一刻想到
I had a moment today and I thought that
如果我现在能改变时间线
maybe if I could change the timeline now,
哪怕是最微不足道的事情
that even in the smallest way
那么  我不知道
that--I don't know.
未来发生的一切会有所不同
That everything in the future would be somehow different.
这就是你不想再办报社的原因
This is why you changed your mind about the newspaper.
当我跟律师谈话的时候
When I talked to the lawyer,
我让她去查了一些潜在的名字
I asked her to check a dozen potential names,
你猜哪一个是唯一能用的
and guess which one was the only one that cleared.
"中城市民"
The "Central City Citizen."
我知道它背后有负担  但那只是一个名字
I know it's got baggage, but it's just a name.
是吗  我们看着那报纸头版
Is it? I mean, we've been looking at that front page
已经有四年了
for four years.
闪电侠失踪  消失于危机之中
"Flash Missing, Vanishes in Crisis."
我就是写那篇文章的人  巴里
And I'm the one that writes that article, Barry.
我只是觉得  我不知道
I just thought that, I don't know,
要是我一开始不去创办那报纸  那么
maybe if I don't start the paper, that--
爱瑞丝  这是你的梦想
Iris, this is your dream,
这座城需要像你一样的人
and the city needs somebody like you.
可是  巴里  看它把我们带到了哪里
Yeah, but, Barry, look where it gets us.
这是目前时间线上诺拉的回忆
These are Nora's memories right now in this timeline
是在她干涉之后的
after she interfered.
我们继续寻找传送门  好吗
Let's keep looking for the portal, okay?
诺拉需要我们的帮助
Nora needs our help.
他要什么我要什么
I'll have whatever he's having.
我现在想要的是打快车离开这里
All I want to order right now is a Lyft out of here,
但是这家酒吧里没有任何信号
but I get no bars in this bar,
所以我或许只好用老办法离开这里
so maybe I'll just have to leave the old-fashioned way
打开缺口走人
and breach on out of here.
听着  西斯科  我
Look, Cisco, I'm...
对不起  我骗你了
Sorry I lied to you.
别向我道歉
Don't apologize to me.
向外面还在等着解药的
Apologize to all the meta-humans out there
所有的超能力者道歉
still waiting for a cure,
向他们能自由选择能力去留的权力道歉
for their right to choose if they want these powers or not.
在我成为伸缩人之前
Before I was The Elongated Man,
当我还是无名小辈拉尔夫·德比的时候
when I was just nobody Ralph Dibny,
我可以在任何时候做我想做的事
I could do whatever I wanted whenever I wanted,
但是没有任何朋友一起做这些事
but I didn't have any friends to do those things with.
所以我想如果  我们可以休息一晚
So I just thought if, uh, we're getting a night off
停止追捕蝉  我们可以
from stopping Cicada, we could just
外出  然后
go out and...
找点乐子
have some fun, you know?
这我也想要
And I want that too,
但要在我们解决这个解药的问题之后
but after we figure out this cure.
你知道吗  我妈妈的朋友道格
You know, my mom's friend Doug,
他有一句名言
he had a saying.
假如你总是等待时机去好好生活
"If you're always waiting to live your life,
你会等到死亡那一刻都还没有开始
you're gonna die before it starts."
至于道格  这道理他最懂
And Doug, he would know.
他可是开磨冰车的
He operated a zamboni.
愿他安息
May he rest in peace.
好的  我要出去一下
All right, I'ma go outside,
看下我可不可以把手臂伸到足够高
see if I can stretch my arm high enough
给你带来手机信号
to get you some cell phone service.
免费的黑暗风暴
Dark and Stormy on the house.
我看起来很可怜吗
Do I look that pathetic?
你看起来像和我一样属于这里的
You look like you belong here about as much as I do.
我开始以为来这里是为了开会的
Thought I was coming here for a business meeting.
你做什么工作  销售皮革
What do you do, sell leather?
-不是  -纹身艺术家
- Nope. - Tattoo artist.
-也不是  -雇佣枪手
- Mm-mm. - Gun for hire.
相信我
Trust me.
如果我告诉你  你也不会相信的
You wouldn't believe me if I told you.
我是摄影师
Well, I'm a photographer,
所以看起来我们都有点迷失方向了
so it looks like we're both a little lost.
所以你的理由是什么
So what's your excuse?
摄影暂时还没有让我变得富有
Taking pictures hasn't made me rich, yet,
所以我当酒保来付房租
so I bartend to pay rent.
我姐姐介绍我来这里的
My sister hooked me up here.
但是忘了告诉我是在地狱工作
Forgot to mention I'd be working in hell.
姐妹
Sisters.
假如我研究两个姐妹的基因
If I looked at the DNA of two siblings,
一个成为了超能力者  然而另一个没有
one who became a meta and one who didn't,
我可以得到一个最接近的基因匹配
I would have a close enough genetic match
来隔离控制超能力基因的
to isolate the part of the genome
那个基因组
that controls meta-genes.
对不起  我刚刚是不是说得很大声
I'm sorry, did I just say that out loud?
是的  很大声
Yeah, you did.
我  我只是  我
I-I just--that--I--
-西斯科  -卡蜜拉
- Cisco. - Camilla.
-很高兴认识你  -我也很高兴认识你
- Nice to meet you. - Nice to meet you.
我到处都找不到传送门
I can't find the portal anywhere.
我甚至不能从诺拉这天的回忆里出来
I can't even get out of Nora's memories of this one day.
巴里  躲起来
Barry, get down!
诺拉有麻烦了  格蕾丝的防御机制
Nora's in trouble. Grace's defense mechanisms
神经活动
一定在攻击她
must be attacking her.
不止她一个人有麻烦
She's not the only one who's in trouble.
我们必须把他们全部人都弄出来
We need to get them out of there now.
这是诺拉的防御机制
It's Nora's defense mechanism.
我现在应该怎么做
What am I supposed to do now?
你好
Hello?
-诺拉  是你吗  -凯特琳
- Nora, is that you? - Caitlyn!
太棒了  我跟你说过内心活动缓冲器2.0
Yes, I told you the M.A.D. 2.0
可以完成紧急无线信号的工作
could complete your emergency beacon.
诺拉  你父母进入你的记忆中了
Uh, Nora, your parents went into your memories.
让我联系下他们
Uh, let me conference them in.
什么  我父母去哪了
Sorry, my parents went where?
-爱瑞丝·韦斯特爱伦  -妈  爸
- Iris West-Allan. - Mom? Dad?
诺拉  你还好吗
Nora, are you okay?
听着  我们有个重大发现
So listen. We made an important discovery.
能让你们离开那里
To get you out of there.
传送门隐藏在感知空隙
The portals are hidden in perception gaps.
你记住的东西是以你想要的方式存在
Things that you remember the way you want them to be,
而不是它们真正的面目
not the way they actually were.
因为你在拒绝  或者你的感知
'Cause you're in denial or your perception
受到愤怒或者其他情绪的影响
was colored by anger or what have you.
所以这些防御机制  它们由神经元组成
So these defense mechanisms, they're composed of synapses.
如果你能打破假象记忆中的神经元
If you can break down the synapses in the false memory,
这样能揭开真实的记忆
that will reveal the real memory
神经元震动就会显示出传送门
and the synaptic jolt will expose the portal.
好的  那我们怎么做呢
Okay, so--okay, well, how do we do that?
我们等下打给你们
Well, uh, we'll have to call you back.
你都要烧坏了
You're burning up.
喂
Hello?
感知空隙
Perception gaps.
玩偶之家
The dollhouse.
我们怎么知道哪个记忆不是真的
How do we know which memories weren't real?
当然  爱瑞丝  是反派大厅
Of course... Iris, it's the Hall of Villains.
你和诺拉
You and Nora.
巴里  我还是抑制了诺拉的超能力
Barry, I still dampen Nora's power.
她还是会长大了恨我  这是我的未来
She still grows up hating me. This is my future.
不不  不是的
No, no, it's not.
这只是记忆  是一个伤心又生气的
It's just a memory, one warped from the perspective
离家出走的小孩扭曲的记忆
of a sad, angry, little kid that ran away from home.
你没明白吗  我们在这看到的那个人
Don't you get it? That person that we saw in there,
诺拉告诉我们的那个歹毒的妈妈
the bad mom that Nora told us about,
她在任何时间线都不存在
she doesn't even exist in any timeline.
我告诉过你  你将来是不同的
I told you you had to be different in the future,
但我错了
but I was wrong.
你不必改变自己
You don't have to change who you are.
你甚至不必改变你的报纸的名字
You don't even have to change the name of your newspaper.
我知道任何有你的未来都是好的未来
I know any future with you in it is gonna be a good one.
你也要相信
You just gotta believe that too.
你们在这干什么
What are you doing here?
这个记忆不是真的
Please, this memory isn't real.
你叔叔的房子  我认为不是这样的
Your uncle's house, I don't think it's really like this.
赶紧吃完  孩子
Okay, better eat up, kiddo.
今天可是个大日子
We got a big day--
格蕾丝  趴下
Grace, get down!
我哪都看不到传送门
I don't see the portal anywhere.
巴里  真的有用
Barry, it's working!
死亡  失败
Death. Failure.
又一个破碎的家庭
Another broken family.
这就是我留给你的遗产
This is the legacy I gave you.
没人能破坏我的家庭  你个混蛋
Nobody breaks up my family, you son of a bitch.
不
Oh, no.
你丢了你的玩具
You dropped your toy.
我只是想看看那个博物馆
I just wanted to see the museum.
我知道  宝贝  但你出走了
I know, honey, but you ran away.
我不知道你去哪了
I didn't know where you went.
我担心你可能会受伤
I was afraid you could have gotten hurt.
你说那个博物馆能让你想起来爸爸
You said that the museum reminded you of Dad
因为爸爸是闪电侠的头号粉丝
'cause Dad was the Flash's number one fan.
所以我想看看
So I wanted to see it
因为我也很喜欢闪电侠
'cause I love the Flash too.
不公平
It's not fair.
我知道  宝贝  我知道不公平
I know, honey. I know it's not fair.
我爱你  诺拉
I love you, Nora.
你爸爸也很爱你
Your dad loved you too.
非常非常爱你
So, so much.
过来  宝贝
Come here, girl.
快  我们得走了
Come on. We gotta go.
我们去找诺拉
Let's go get Nora.
格蕾丝  我知道你很害怕
Grace, I know you're afraid.
你觉得你再不会像和叔叔在一起那天
You think that you'll never be as happy as you were
那样开心
that day with your uncle.
这就是为什么你记忆中它是完美的
That's why you try to remember it as perfect,
但没有那么完美的东西  格蕾丝
but things can be that good, Grace.
你得醒过来
You just have to wake up.
然后你和我和我父母
And then you and me and my parents,
我们都能帮你和你叔叔在一起
we can all help your uncle together.
你是个骗子
You're a liar.
格蕾丝
Grace.
或许没有人在乎你
Maybe you don't have anyone who cares about you,
但有人在乎我
but I have someone who cares about me,
我是唯一一个能帮他的
and I'm the only one who can help him.
妈
Mom.
她不会跟来了
She's not coming.
-什么  -快
- What? - Hurry!
快  快
Come on. Come on.
他们没事
They're okay.
神经震动正常
Neural oscillations are normal.
你们三个都很健康
You three are perfectly healthy.
我们觉得我们已经想通了
Oh, and we think we've figured out
你们俩怎么进入诺拉脑中的
how you two ended up in Nora's brain.
暗物质扫描
格蕾丝脑中有个全是暗物质的卫星碎片
That is a satellite shard full of dark matter in Grace's head.
我的天
Mon dieu.
有时医生也会因为移除风险太大
Sometimes surgeons leave a piece of shrapnel
在病人的脑中留下弹片
in a patient's brain if it's too dangerous to remove,
我们认为暗物质正在渗出
and we think that the dark matter was seeping out
在她的大脑周边建立了一个屏障
to create a barrier around her brain.
只要它在我们就回不去
We can't go back in as long as it's there.
太危险了
It's too dangerous.
我们得再找到一个阻止蝉的方法
Well, we need to find another way to stop Cicada.
我觉得或许我能帮上忙
I think I might be able to help with that.
这是德怀尔房子的内部
It's the inside of Dwyer's house.
-该死  -我是说很好
- Damn. - I mean, that's great.
为什么你抛开我们行动  我们计划好的
But why did you go in without us? We had a plan.
我知道
No, I know, um...
你懂的  知道机器已经准备好了
You know, just with the machine being ready
而蝉还在逍遥法外
and knowing that Cicada was still out there,
我大概只是  有点过激了
I guess I just... I got a little excessive.
但不只是这个原因  对吧
It's not the only reason, though, right?
是为了保护她的秘密
It was protecting her secret.
是什么秘密
What secret is that?
她在孩童时对她母亲的情感
Well, her feelings for her mother when she was a child.
肯定是痛苦的记忆
Must be painful memories.
是那样吗  诺拉
Is that correct, Nora?
对  没错
Yeah, exactly.
好了  让我们从这个线索开始追查
Okay, um, let's get started on this lead.
干得好  诺拉
Good job, Nora.
谢谢
Thanks.
艾伦先生  为了记录今天的活动
Monsieur Allen, just for my records of today's events,
诺拉使用的防卫装置是什么
what was the defense mechanism Nora was using?
是博物馆里的其中一套战衣
It was one of the costumes from the museum.
什么战衣
What costume?
逆闪
The Reverse Flash.
惊喜
Surprise!
第一天使用新办公室快乐
Happy first day in your new office.
你们真好
You're so sweet.
你决定好给报纸取什么名字了吗
So have you decided what you're gonna name the paper?
我不知道
I don't know.
"中城市民"听起来很不错
"Central City Citizen" has a certain ring to it.
-你确定吗  -你说的对
- You sure? - Yeah, you were right.
未来不总是我们所以为的样子
Future isn't always what it seems.
我们会决定它的走向
We decide what it gets to be.
我必须告诉你们一件小事
So, um, I just have to tell you one little thing.
看到下面那个横标了吗
See that ledger down there?
创办于2021年
那是我的时间里报纸创办的时间
That's the year the paper was founded in my time.
2021年
2021.
两年后
That's two years from now.
创办于2019年
你们已经改变未来了
You're changing the future already.
我必须去找西斯科
Hey, um, I gotta find Cisco,
我们待会见  好吗
but I'll see you guys later, all right?
好的
Okay.
我们回去吧
Let's head back.
-妈妈  -什么事
- Mom? - Yeah?
爸爸告诉我你看到的记忆
Dad told me about the memory that you saw.
我知道那不是真的  诺拉
I know it wasn't real, Nora,
但那必定来源于真实的存在
but it must have come from a very real place.
你肯定是非常地气我才会那样地看待我
You must have been so angry with me to see me that way.
我一直都很愤怒
I was angry all the time.
愤怒于没有父亲
Angry for not getting to have a dad,
愤怒于没人能理解我的感受
angry 'cause nobody seemed to understand what I was feeling.
而不管你做了什么或说了什么  妈妈
And it didn't matter what you did or said, Mom.
我都会一直生你的气
I was always gonna be angry at you...
因为你在那
because you were there.
诺拉  你经历了很多
You're going through a lot, Nora.
但你也是
But so were you.
我是说  我以为你在试着阻止我做自己
I mean, I thought you were trying to stop me from being me,
但你是在阻止我成为爸爸
but you were trying to stop me from being Dad.
我是说  得到和他一样的结果
I mean, ending up like him.
你们从小到大都在一起
You guys had a whole life together
还有个孩子  然后他就消失了
and a child, and he vanished.
我无法想像你有多难受
I-I can't imagine how hard that must have been for you.
而且自那天起  你
And from that day, you...
你都在保护我
you were protecting me.
我现在理解了
I-I get that now.
所以我很抱歉  不管是那时还是
So sorry for the way that I treated you,
我刚到这时对待你的态度
both back then and now when I first got here.
你不该遭受那样的对待
You didn't deserve that.
谢谢
Thank you.
你是个了不起的女人  诺拉·韦斯特艾伦
You're an amazing woman, Nora West-Allen.
我会一直爱你
I will always love you,
不管是过去  现在  还是未来
past, present, and future.
妈妈  我也爱你
I love you too, Mom.
保守秘密很艰难  但当你回想起
It's hard to keep a secret, but it's a lot easier
保守秘密的原因时会让你轻松很多
when you're reminded why you're doing it.
-真的吗  -对
- Ready? - Yeah.
我遇到一个人  她告诉她会不惜一切
I met someone who told me that she would do anything
保护她的家庭
to protect her family.
她帮我看清了  我也会那么做
She helped me see that... so would I.
我的父母不能知道你在帮我阻止蝉
My parents can't know that you're helping me stop Cicada.
风险太大了
There's too much at risk.
而我会不惜一切地保护他们
And I'll do anything to protect them.
即使要撒谎
Even lie.
医疗中心
骗子
Liar.
骗子  骗子
Liar. Liar.
诺拉向我说谎了
Nora lied to me.
她会付出代价
She'll pay.
他们全部会付出代价
They'll all pay.
道格是对的
Doug was right.
到外面  去溜冰什么的
Going out there, doing the ice skating thing,
绝对是正确的选择
that was definitely the right thing to do.
是的  道格  愿他安息
Yeah, all Doug, may he rest in peace.
为死去的他倒杯酒
Let's pour one out for the guy.
卡蜜拉
卡蜜拉  那个酒保
Camilla? The bartender?
-不好意思  -老兄  干得好
- Uh, excuse me. - Dude, nice.
-好吧  好吧  -对
- All right, all right. - Yeah.
你们在超能力者解药上
Hey, did you guys make a breakthrough
有突破吗
with the meta-human cure?
有  我设法找到一对兄弟姐妹
We did. I managed to locate a pair of
一个有超能力一个没有
meta-non-meta siblings,
这个解药  马上就完成了
so this cure, it's as good as done.
很好  因为我一直在考虑
All right, good, because I've been thinking.
我想要对蝉使用解药
I want to use the cure on Cicada.